# B. Rhiannon Hays, M.Ed.

- ESL Educator -

#### contact

## professional bio

(010) 2038-9670



rhiannon.clintkorea@gmail.com



Ilsan, South Korea



Secondary English educator with 7+ years of experience managing students and classroom. My teaching philosophy focuses on the principle that each student learns in his or her own unique way. I employ multiple methods of teaching in my classroom to engage and reach every student so that no one student is left behind. I want each student that enters my classroom to feel recognized and accepted. I work tirelessly to help students meet their full potential.

## experience

#### NATIVE ENGLISH TEACHER

Winny English Education / Ilsan, South Korea / 2020 - Present

- Instructs English speaking, grammar, reading and writing courses
- Designs all curriculum, lesson plans and assessments for class
- Manages classroom routine and structure
- Creates themes, contests and activities to enhance English retention
- Specializes in designing English curriculum through interactive play
- Communicates students' levels and behavior to co-teacher and parents

#### **ENGLISH INSTRUCTOR**

Ellin Nature English Institute / Ilsan, South Korea / 2018 - 2020

- Taught English speaking, grammar, reading and writing
- Managed classroom environment and student behavior
- Designed activities, lesson plans, contests and field trips for students
- Communicated student progress to parents
- Specialized in English learning through drama practice
- Responsible for 40+ classes per week

#### **ESL EDUCATOR**

Jungchul English Academy / Jinhae, South Korea / 2015 - 2018

- Taught English conversation and grammar to K-12 and adult students
- Responsible for 40+ classes per week
- Monitored and managed student learning and behavior
- Designed activities, lesson plans and speaking contests for students
- Communicated student progress to parents and co-teachers

## education

University of Central Oklahoma

- M.Ed. in SECONDARY EDUCATION - 2015
- B.A. in ENGLISH 2010

## key skills

Classroom Management

Classroom Media Operation

**Lesson Planning** 

**Conflict Resolution Training** 

Differentiated Instruction

Empathy

### certifications

■ TEFL/TESOL – 150 hours August 2014